interactionstudios.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy | InterAction studios

**WEBSITE**

  1. We do not collect personally identifiable information, except where you are expressly asked to supply this information yourself. InterAction studios will treat any such information in confidence and will not make it available to any third party, except if required to do so by law.
  2. We may use the contact information that you have provided on this website in order to send you information pertaining to your purchased games and their updates. You may opt out of such communications at any time.
  3. We do not have access to, maintain an archive of, or process any form of credit card information in any way.
  4. We use cookies to remember your authorization code, as well as maintain anonymous traffic statistics.
  5. We do not create, bundle, or deliver through our products software of a trojan, viral, adware, or spyware nature.

**PC/MAC/LINUX GAMES**

  1. We do not directly or indirectly collect, process, or transmit any personally identifiable information from your desktop PC.
  2. We use the authorization code that you have supplied in-game in order to upload your career progress and high scores to our website.

**ANDROID GAMES**

  1. We do not directly collect, process, or transmit any personally identifiable information from your Android device. Nevertheless, we sometimes use other companies' services (for example, to show ads), and such information may be collected by them.
  2. If you purchase the game using your Apple Account, we do not have access to or knowledge of information in that account.
  3. We use Google Mobile Ads to display ads in ad-supported (non-purchased) builds of the game. Google's privacy policy can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy). You can remove ads by purchasing ("unlocking") the game.

**IOS GAMES**

  1. We do not directly collect, process, or transmit any personally identifiable information from your iOS device. Nevertheless, we sometimes use other companies' services (for example, to show ads), and such information may be collected by them.
  2. If you purchase the game using your Google Account, we do not have access to or knowledge of information in that account.
  3. We use Google Mobile Ads to display ads in ad-supported (non-purchased) builds of the game. Google's privacy policy can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy). You can remove ads by purchasing ("unlocking") the game.

**YOUR INFORMATION**

  1. We use the information you supply to us in order to identify you when using our services (for instance, when you have lost your authorization code).
  2. We use the contact information your have provided to send you e-mail (but only if you have allowed us to do so).
  3. We use certain information (such as your IP address) to protect against fraud and abuse of our services.
  4. We do not disclose or sell this information to anyone.
  5. We will immediately delete any stored information pertaining to yourself upon your request.

©2002-2018 Konstantinos Prouskas and InterAction studios. All rights reserved. Terms of use. Privacy Policy.
